<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<document xmlns="http://di.tamu.edu/DRI/1.0/" xmlns:i18n="http://apache.org/cocoon/i18n/2.1" version="1.1">
<body>
<div id="file.news.div.news" n="news" rend="primary">
<head>Digital Archives of Literacy Narratives</head>
<p>
  <hi rend="bold">Welcome!</hi> The Digital Archives of Literacy Narratives (DALN) is a publicly available
  archive of personal literacy narratives in a variety of formats (text, video, audio)
  that together provide a historical record of the literacy practices and values
  of contributors, as those practices and values change. The project is jointly directed by faculty from The Ohio State University and Georgia State University.
</p>
<p>
  The DALN invites people of all ages, races, communities, backgrounds, and interests
  to contribute stories about how &#x2014; and in what circumstances &#x2014; they read, write, and compose meaning,
  and how they learned to do so (or helped others learn). We welcome personal narratives about 
  reading and composing all kinds of texts, both formal
  and informal: diaries, blogs, poetry, music and musical lyrics, fan zines,
  school papers, videos, sermons, gaming profiles, speeches, chatroom exchanges,
  text messages, letters, stories, photographs, etc. We also invite contributors
  to supplement their narratives with samples of their own writing (papers, letters, zines, speeches,
  etc.) and compositions (music, photographs, videos, sound recordings, etc.).
</p>
<p>
   If you would like more detailed information about creating a literacy narrative and contributing it
   to the DALN, please visit our <hi rend="bold"><xref target="http://dalnresources.org.ohio-state.edu/contents.html">resources and help pages</xref></hi>. Also, for DALN-related news, interviews, and other important resources, visit <hi rend="bold"><xref target="https://thedaln.wordpress.com">The DALN Blog</xref></hi>.
</p>
<p>
  To submit your literacy narrative, you must first <hi rend="bold"><xref target="/register">register</xref></hi> with
  the DALN, a simple process that requires only a valid e-mail
  address. Once you have registered, you can <hi rend="bold"><xref target="/login">login</xref></hi> and 
  <hi rend="bold"><xref target="/submissions">submit a narrative</xref></hi>.
</p>
  <!-- HLU 081117 -->
<p id="DALN-main-links">
  <hi rend="bigBold">
  <xref target="/register">Register</xref>
  &#xa0;&#xa0;&#xa0;|&#xa0;&#xa0;&#xa0;
  <xref target="/login">Login</xref>
  &#xa0;&#xa0;&#xa0;|&#xa0;&#xa0;&#xa0;
  <xref target="/submissions">Submit a Narrative</xref>
  &#xa0;&#xa0;&#xa0;&#xa0;|&#xa0;&#xa0;&#xa0;&#xa0;
  <xref target="http://dalnresources.org.ohio-state.edu/contents.html">Consult Resources</xref>
  &#xa0;&#xa0;&#xa0;|&#xa0;&#xa0;&#xa0;
  <xref target="http://dalnresources.org.ohio-state.edu/partners.html">View Contributing Partners</xref>
  </hi>
</p>
<p><xref target="http://dalnresources.org.ohio-state.edu/WhyRegisterDALN.html">Why do we ask you to register?</xref></p>
</div>
</body>
<options/>
<meta>
<userMeta/>
<pageMeta/>
<repositoryMeta/>
</meta>
</document>